hulkshare.biz 2012-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Hulk Share

**Data Privacy**

Thank you for visiting our website. This privacy policy tells you how to use the personal information collected on this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or send any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but the changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information to move forward, not retroactively. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to ensure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

**Information Collection**

We may collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by visitors. The information you provide is used to meet the specific order. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it differently, for example, to add to one of our mailing lists. 

**Cookie / Tracking Technology**

The site may use cookies and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookies and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information can not be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. information tracking cookies total and may be shared with third parties. The Site or the advertisers on the site may use cookies and / or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. 

**Distribution Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We can do so when: (1) permitted or required by law, or (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personal information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allows you to switch to other mails. 

**Privacy Contact Information**

If you have questions, concerns or comments about our privacy policy, please contact me admin@hulkshare.biz 

We do not follow what you do online, therefore no log is kept of your activites.

We use your IP address to help diagnose and fix problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

We will not disclose, rent or sell your email address to anyone.
